<resources>
    <!-- upload id document -->
    <string name="title_upload_id_document">Upload ID Document</string>
    <string name="upload_photo_of_your_document">Please upload photo of your travel document.</string>
    <string name="following_item_must_be_clearly_visible">The following items must be clearly visible</string>
    <string name="list_of_document_id">. face photo\n. name\n. address\n. date of birth\n. date of expiry</string>
    <string name="face_photo">face photo</string>

    <!-- terms and conditions -->
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_description">The software you are about to use functions as a free, and open source.\n\nWhile the software has undergone beta testing and continues to be improved by feedback from the open-source user and developer community, we cannot guarantee that there will be no bugs in the software. You acknowledge that your use of this software is at your own discretion and in compliance with all applicable laws. You are responsible for safekeeping your passwords, and any other codes you use to access the software.\n\nTo the fullest extent permitted by law, this software is provided as is and no representations or warranties can be made of any kind, express or implied, including but not limited to the warranties of merchantability, fitness or a particular purpose and noninfringement. You assume any and all risks associated with the use of the software. In no event shall the authors of the software, employees and affiliates of Truong Thanh JAPAN, copyright holders, or Truong Thanh JAPAN, Co,.Ltd. be held liable for any claim, damages or other liability, whether in an action of contract, tort, or otherwise, arising from, out of or in connection with the software. We reserve the right to modify this disclaimer from time to time.</string>
    <string name="select_term_and_conditions">I agree with </string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions"><u>terms and conditions</u></string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

    <!-- tutorial -->
    <string name="tutorial_welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="tutorial_start">start</string>
    <string name="tutorial_form_submit">send</string>
    <string name="tutorial_form_desc">* Provide your email address to activate your account.\n* Once you submit this form, then we will send you a confirmation email.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_verification_code_desc">* Provide verification code which was sent by email.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_password_on_import_desc">* Provide password which was sent  by email when you created an account on the first time.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_end_desc">Your account has been activated.\nPlease enjoy!</string>
    <string name="app_start">start</string>

    <!-- general -->
    <string name="point_name">POINT</string>
    <string name="coin_name">COIN</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email address</string>
    <string name="first_name">First name</string>
    <string name="middle_name">Middle name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last name</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="cell_phone_number">Cell phone number</string>
    <string name="dob">Date of birth</string>
    <string name="qr_code">QR Code</string>
    <string name="complete">Complete</string>
    <string name="transaction_type">send/receive</string>
    <string name="transaction_status">status</string>
    <string name="tab">tab</string>
    <string name="verification_code">code</string>
    <string name="password_on_import">password</string>
    <string name="not_set">Not set</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_title">ERROR</string>
    <string name="no_transaction_data">There is no transaction data.</string>
    <string name="set_amount_desc">set amount</string>
    <string name="hint_receive_amount">amount</string>
    <string name="hint_send_amount">amount</string>
    <string name="send_by_qr">Scan Code</string>
    <string name="send_by_email">By Email Address</string>
    <string name="send_email_form_desc">* Provide email address you want to send point/coin to.</string>
    <string name="send_successfully_executed">The payment has been submitted.\nPlease wait a moment until the transaction be processed.</string>
    <string name="profile_successfully_updated">Your profile has been updated successfully.</string>
    <string name="push_notification">Push Notification</string>
    <string name="email_notification">Email Notification</string>
    <string name="upload_your_id_document">Upload Your ID Document</string>
    <string name="under_review_for_id_document">Under review for ID Document</string>
    <string name="id_document_was_approved">ID Document was approved</string>
    <string name="message_note_disabled_send_for_id">You cannot use this function until your ID is verified.</string>
    <string name="message_note_upload_id_for_disabling_edit_profile">Once you upload images, you will not be able to edit your profile.</string>
    <string name="successfully_uploaded">Successfully uploaded</string>
    <string name="national_code_should_be">National code should be 81(Japan) or 84(Vietnam)</string>
    <string name="default_dob">01/Jan/1990</string>
    <string name="address_place_holder">House No, Street No, City, Country, Postal Code</string>
    <string name="dot">•</string>

    <!-- privacy policy -->
    <string name="privacy_policy"><b>Privacy Policy</b></string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_description">
        \nThis Privacy Policy describes the ways in which we (TTJ Co.,Ltd., inclusive of subsidiaries) collect, use, disclose and protect personal information.
        \n\nPrivacy Policy applies to information that we collect when you access or use TTJ’s website or mobile apps (collectively, “SENtoken Project Services”) or otherwise interact with us as described below.
    </string>
    <string name="collection_of_information"><b>\nCollection of information</b>
        <b>\n\nInformation provided from you</b>
        \n\nWe collect information that are directly provided from you. We collect information when you make an online account, complete a transaction, fill out a form, respond to surveys, post a message on our forum or otherwise communicate with us.
        <b>\n\nThe types of information we may collect</b>
    </string>
    <string name="the_types_of_information_we_may_collect_one">Contact information: such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address.</string>
    <string name="the_types_of_information_we_may_collect_two">Financial information: such as bank account numbers, credit card numbers and cryptor currency account information.</string>
    <string name="the_types_of_information_we_may_collect_three">Government issued ID number: driver’s license or passport information.</string>
    <string name="the_types_of_information_we_may_collect_four">Biographic or demographic information : such as your date of birth, gender, occupation, employment status.</string>
    <string name="collection_of_information_one">
        <b>\nInformation we collect from other sources</b>
        \n\nWe may collect information from other sources and combine that with information collected through the SENtoken Project Services.
        \ne.g. We collect your nonpublic personal information from third parties including identity verification services.
        \n\n<b>Information We collect automatically</b>
        \n\nWe collect information automatically when you visit or use the SENtoken Project Services.
    </string>
    <string name="information_we_collect_automatically_one">
        <b>Transaction information</b> : we collect information about the transaction you complete via the SENtoken Project Services, including the amount of funds associated with a trade, the types of trades executed and other transaction information.
    </string>
    <string name="information_we_collect_automatically_two">
        <b>Location information</b> :  With your prior consent, we may collect precise geolocation information from your mobile device when you visit or use our mobile app. Please refer to “Your Choice” below for more information.
    </string>
    <string name="information_we_collect_automatically_three">
        <b>Transaction information</b> : We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access the SENtoken Project Services, including device identifiers, mobile network information, type of operating system, and the type of browser used. We also log information about your use of the SENtoken Project Services, including access times, pages viewed, IP address, other standard web log data, and the page visited before and after navigating to our websites.
    </string>
    <string name="information_we_collect_automatically_four">
        <b>Cookie and similar tracking technologies</b> : We may use cookies or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you visit the SENtoken Project Services including information of your browsing behavior. Cookies are small data files transferred from our web servers to your computer or mobile device that enable us to, for example, capture how you arrived at the SENtoken Project Services, when you return, which pages on the SENtoken Project Services you visit, and to recognize that you are already logged on when we receive a page request from your browser.
    </string>
    <string name="collection_of_information_two">
        <b>\nUse of information</b>
        \n\nWe may use your information in the following ways:
    </string>
    <string name="user_of_information_one">Provide the SENtoken Project Services and customer support;</string>
    <string name="user_of_information_two">Process transactions and send notices about your transactions;</string>
    <string name="user_of_information_three">Manage your account(s) and send technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;</string>
    <string name="user_of_information_four">Resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;</string>
    <string name="user_of_information_five">Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and enforce our user agreements;</string>
    <string name="user_of_information_six">Personalize, measure and improve the SENtoken Project Services;</string>
    <string name="user_of_information_seven">Deliver marketing and promotional offers on behalf of SENtoken and others, including via SMS, voice calls or email;</string>
    <string name="user_of_information_eight">Link or combine your personal information with information we obtain from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service;</string>
    <string name="user_of_information_nine">Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected, to the extent such purpose is necessarily contemplated by the collection of such information or as otherwise notified in the SENtoken Project Services at the time of collection.</string>
    <string name="collection_of_information_three">
        <b>\nDisclosure of information</b>
        \n\nWe may disclose any information we collect about you including nonpublic information and other information we collect to nonaffiliated third parties, whether you are currently our customer or was our customer in the past. We may make such disclosures:
    </string>
    <string name="disclosure_number_one">(1) To service providers that perform marketing services on our behalf;</string>
    <string name="disclosure_number_two">(2) For our everyday business purposes, such as to process transactions, maintain accounts, respond to court orders and legal investigations or report to credit bureaus.</string>
    <string name="sub_disclosure_number_two_one">For example, in connection with our everyday business purposes, we may share information about you as follows:</string>
    <string name="sub_disclosure_number_two_two">With any party you intend to distribute funds to, or that intends to distribute funds to you, via the SENtoken Project Services, including information about whether your account is active and whether the account has been verified.</string>
    <string name="sub_disclosure_number_two_three">With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to your information to carry out work on our behalf. These service providers help with our business operations such as fraud prevention and technology services.</string>
    <string name="sub_disclosure_number_two_four">When we believe, in our sole discretion, that the disclosure of your information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of or enforce our user agreements or other policies and agreements.</string>
    <string name="sub_disclosure_number_two_five">In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of SENtoken project’s assets, financing or acquisition or all or a portion of our business to another</string>
    <string name="sub_disclosure_number_two_six">With your consent or at your discretion</string>
    <string name="disclosure_number_three">(3) If we are under a duty to disclose or share your information to comply with our legal obligations.</string>
    <string name="collection_of_information_four">
        \nOther than in connection with a merger, sale of SENtoken project is assets, financing or acquisition, we will not sell or rent any of your information to third parties for their own marketing purposes.
        \n\nPlease note that third parties that support our customer identification and anti-fraud controls may retain and use information about you to perform services on our behalf and to improve their services. By using our Services, you consent to the retention and use of such information by these providers to improve their services.
        \n\nWe may also share aggregated or de-identified information with our affiliated companies or nonaffiliated third parties, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.
        \n\n<b>Analysis service provided by others companies</b>
        \n\nWe allow other entities to provide analytics services on our behalf. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies to collect information about your use of SENtoken project service, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages and links clicked. This information may be used by SENtoken project to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, and better understand your online activity.
        \n\n<b>Security</b>
        \n\nWe implement reasonable security practices and procedures to help protect the confidentiality and security of your information, including any nonpublic personal information. We protect your information using reasonable physical, technical and administrative security measures, including by limiting access to your information to employees with a need to know such information.
        \n\n<b>Your choice</b>
    </string>
    <string name="your_choice_one">
        <b>Account Information:</b> You may access and review or update your online account information at any time by logging into your account and viewing your profile. If you want to close your account, please contact us at http://www.ttjworld.com/#/contact-us. However, please note that if you close your account, we may retain your information as required by law or for our legitimate business purposes, such as to collect fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, prevent fraud or enforce our user agreements.
    </string>
    <string name="your_choice_two">
        <b>Communications Preferences:</b> You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from SENtoken project by following the instructions in those communications. If you opt out of receiving promotional communications, we may still send you transactional or relationship messages, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.
    </string>
    <string name="your_choice_three">
        <b>Location:</b> Our mobile applications may collect precise geolocation information from your mobile device with your prior consent. If you initially consent to our collection of location information, you may be able to subsequently stop the collection of this information through your device operating system settings. You may also stop our collection of location information by following the standard uninstall process to remove our mobile applications from your device.
    </string>
    <string name="your_choice_four">
        <b>Cookies:</b> We use both session and persistent cookies. Session cookies expire when you log out of your account or close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your computer or mobile device until you erase them or they otherwise expire. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. You are free to decline most of our cookies if your browser or browser add-on permits, but choosing to remove or disable our cookies may interfere with your use and functionality of the SENtoken Services. Additionally, we may use certain persistent cookies that are not affected by your browser settings, but will use such cookies solely for identity verification and fraud prevention purposes. For more information about cookies and how to block, delete or disable them, please refer to your browser instructions, or contact us at http://www.ttjworld.com/#/contact-us.
    </string>
    <string name="contact_us">
        \n<b>Contact Us</b>
        \n\nIf you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at http://www.ttjworld.com/#/contact-us.
    </string>

    <!-- error message -->
    <string name="error_default_message">Unknown error occurred.Please retry later.</string>
    <string name="error_cannot_connect_to_server">Error occurred due to network error.Please retry later.</string>
    <string name="error_lockout_message">Sorry for inconvenience.The Server is busy.Please retry later.</string>
    <string name="error_validation_email_address">email address format is invalid.</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_verification_code">This code is wrong.Please check your email again.</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password_on_import">This password is wrong.Please check your email again sent when you first registered an account.</string>
    <string name="error_device_already_setup">This account has been set up already.Please retry later.</string>
    <string name="error_cannot_update_profile_image">Failed to update profile info due to your profile image was too large.Please retry later.</string>
    <string name="error_cannot_self_send">You cannot send to yourself.</string>
    <string name="error_cannot_send_that_amount">You cannot send that much.</string>
    <string name="error_message_no_such_email_address_user">Sorry.There is no such user account related with the email address.</string>
    <string name="error_message_invalid_long">please input valid number of amount.</string>
    <string name="error_permission_denied_on_launch_camera">Cannot activate camera. Please grant authorities to this app.</string>

    <!-- button -->
    <string name="default_positive_button_text">OK</string>
    <string name="default_cancel_button_text">Cancel</string>
    <string name="send_button_text">Send</string>
    <string name="save_button_text">Save</string>
    <string name="image_from_folder">Choose from Library</string>
    <string name="image_from_camera">Take Photo</string>

    <!-- menu -->
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_receive">Receive</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_settings_profile">Your Profile</string>
    <string name="menu_settings_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <!-- function title -->
    <string name="title_set_amount">set amount</string>
    <string name="title_send">send</string>
    <string name="title_settings_profile">Your Profile</string>
    <string name="title_settings_edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="title_settings_notification">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_setting_terms_of_conditions">Terms of Conditions</string>
    <string name="title_setting_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>

    <!-- Notification -->
    <string name="channel_name_default">Default Notification</string>

    <!-- format -->
    <string name="any">%s</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_desc_format">Are you sure you want to send %d %s to %s?</string>
    <!-- Push Notification -->
    <string name="notification_title_receive_payment_notification">Receive Payment</string>
    <string name="notification_body_receive_payment_notification">You received %s %s from %s.</string>
    <string name="notification_title_send_payment_notification">Payment Completed</string>
    <string name="notification_body_send_payment_notification">The payment (%s %s to %s) has been completed successfully.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
